CURRICULUM VITAE

AYESHA FAROOQ

My Contact

ayeshasamreen.fairy@gmail.com

© 0573110989

About Me

An enthusiastic individual with excellent administrative, research, and writing skills having pursued Master of Business Administration in Human Resources (MBA (HR)). Aim to be professionally associated with a growth-oriented organization and to utilize the opportunities that come through by offering every bit of talent and expertise.

Key Skills

- Ability to achieve immediate and long-term goals.
- Strong motivational and leadership skills.
- Excellent communication skills.
- Team Player.
- Multi-tasking.
- Time management.
- · Excellent typing skills.

Education Background

MBA(HR)

IGNOU University, Delhi, India 2018-2021

B.Com(CA)

Alagappa University, Tamil Nadi, India 2014-2017

• Intermediate (Commerce)

International Indian School, Riyadh 2012-2014

• SSC

Al-Yasmin International School, Riyadh 2012-2014

Professional Experience

Admin Assistant at Alif International School, Riyadh

Sep 2021- June 2022

- Managing administrative duties and tasks.
- Performing Digital marketing for the institution.
- Handling queries and responding to emails.
- · Inventory and file management.
- Data management and HR duties.
- Dealing with Admissions, Transfer certificates and Bonafide certificates.
- Performing basic accounting tasks.

Content Writing Intern at Serene Events, India

Apr 2021- May 2021

- Wrote SEO-optimized articles of 4000+ words daily as per the requirements of various clients.
- Creating and editing social media posts for digital marketing of client's website.

Content Writer at Josh Talks, India

July 2020 - Sep 2020

- Wrote 9 SEO-optimized articles of 2000+ words each relating to Personality development and English learning.
- Created a pillar page of 4000+ words to boost website traffic.

Achievements

2014 Awarded with the certificate of academic excellence from Mr. Hamid Ali Rao (Indian Ambassador to Saudi Arabia) in the first and second year of Intermediate.

Technical Skills

- MS Office
- WordPress
- SEO